sup everyone team was only five with a
very special video today and today is
Saturday now I know a lot of you liked
like my food eating videos with my food
I eat themed on Csonka and Kara still
outside hey it's Saturday it's another
Saturday night I mean another sock on
'theme meal I'll bring you guys along
for the ride to stop off for Knuckles we
got did you make in golden crust spicy
beef added as a Echidnas for a red
packaging lock Knuckles I mean this is
this is good I mean he's not gonna
believe this look at that look at
that patty
that is delicious golden my
father's butt cheeks but no know that
the Bobby is yet to come for Bob in fact
you cannot eat a Jamaican beef patty
without of course some good old American
yellow mustard and some amazing ketchup
so those are I will be eating today
Oh pull them for the side I got for me
these dad I got some pumpkin spice
marshmallows go and get like noodles out
of it oh oh damn they smell so good
look at that pumpkin spice and
put that next to the beef patty along
with our got some like rainbow sprinkles
for the sock I guess well Manic I got
some luck
I didn't only have Mountain Dews I just
went down to the store to buy another
green pop it's just called Mountain in a
blue Cup you seen Bob Sonic's oh yeah
these oh oh for Mindy I got some hot dog
onion sauce so I'm just a school like a
little summer write down
come on
one morning come out are you kidding me
oh yeah oh damn that is good
I'm gonna get some lock yellow must up
for this got school it got pakka
put a lock on the Mach most to lie
father not all this go get some
lock oh oh yes oh my God
oh yes Oh mmm damn
gonca Papa gumball flock Queen Lena
garlic I got I got a strawberry suck and
I'm gonna use like that represent Sonia
being as duh
well let's let's get started um oh yes
give me that mmm oh my God give me
more oh yeah mmm so good
look at that gumball that's what they're
for dad I see
[Music]
oh that's so good
oh my God exactly it's a spicy beef
patty mmm
oh my God honey a marshmallow Oh
oh my God Oliver so good oh damn the
marshmallow
oh yes oh that's nice gumball oh oh
yes mmm this is divine
mmm oh yeah
I need more ketchup mustard two
oh yes
I need more mock milk that's one that's
what daddy needs Oh
oh yes oh my God
oh no damn luckily well no I talking do
you play right now
oh yeah I need more mmm oh my God oh yes
on
oh my God I want more mouth noise mmm oh
yes